

- awaisiqbalqadri22@gmail.com
- Stockholm, Sweden
- 🗯 28 years old
- pakistani
- Driving licence
- Stockholm
- +46 76 307 07 64
- Single

Skills

ReactJs, ExpressJs, NodeJs

JavaScript, TypeScript

NextJs

SQL, Postgres

Git, Docker, OpenAPI, prismaORM, mongoDB, TailwindCSS

React Native

CI/CD

EC2 AWS, Cloudflare, S3 AWS,

monorepos, WebSockets, PubSubs, Redis

Languages

English

Swedish

Certification in SFI-3C

Interests

Cricket, Football

Social networks

in @Awais Iqbal Qadri

🥊 @awaisqadri22

Awais Iqbal Qadri

Software developer | DevOps Engineer

I am an enthusiastic and driven Software Engineering graduate with BS (Hons) degree from the University of Gujrat. Perusing my journey as a MERN Stack Developer with 2+ years of professional experience also worked with cloud resources. Experienced working in FinTech.

Education

Computer Science (Master's)

Since September 2022 Univeristy of Gothenburg Göteborg, VG, Sweden Perusing my master's degree in major courses (requirement engineering, functional programming, Advance Web development techniques...)

Software Engineering (Bachelor's)

From September 2015 to September 2019 University of Gujrat Gujrāt, PB, Pakistan

Final year project:

I developed blood donation platform (Web application + mobile apps) using Angular.js as website front end, React Native for hybrid mobile applications development and expressJs for REST API's and mongoDB as database.

Work experience

Freelancing

Since January 2023 Self Employed Stockholm, Sweden

Full stack developer | DevOps Engineer

From January 2021 to December 2022 Morosoft technologies Islambad, Pakistan Worked as full stack developer, using tech stack Nextjs, prismaORM, reactjs, Nodejs, ExpressJs, AWS, React Native, Firebase, Postgres, MongoDB.

Software Developer

From January 2020 to December 2020 Cipher Savvy Rawalpindi, Pakistan Served as a MERN stack developer, developed hybrid mobile applications (iOS+Android) using React Native, react.js for front-end development and expressjs for REST API's.

Front End developer (internee)

From September 2019 to December 2019 IntraSols Islambad, Pakistan I was an internee, working with core php and website front end designing with HTML5, CSS3, BootStrap, jQuery.